var basketball = [
	{
		front: "Clippers",
		back: "Los Angeles"
	}, {
		front: "Lakers",
		back: "Los Angeles"
	}, {
		front: "Warriors",
		back: "Oakland"
	},{
		front: "Trail Blazers",
		back: "Portland"
	}, {
		front: "Suns",
		back: "Phoenix"
	}, {
		front: "Spurs",
		back: "San Antonio"
	}, {
		front: "Celtics",
		back: "Boston"
	}, {
		front: "Nets",
		back: "Brookland"
	}, {
		front: "Nicks",
		back: "New York"
	}, {
		front: "Cavaliers",
		back: "Cleveland"
	}, {
		front: "Heat",
		back: "Miami"
	}, {
		front: "Nuggets",
		back: "Denver"
	}, {
		front: "Mavericks",
		back: "Dallas"
	}
];

module.exports = basketball;